<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../entries2html.xsl" ?>
<entry name="animate" namespace="fn" type="method" return="jQuery" version="1.4">
	<created>1.0</created>

	<signature added="1.0">
		<argument name="properties" type="Object">
			<desc>A map of CSS properties that the animation will move toward.</desc>
		</argument>
		<argument name="duration" type="Option"/>
		<argument name="easing" type="Option"/>
		<argument name="complete" type="Option"/>
	</signature>
	<signature added="1.0">
		<argument name="properties" type="Object">
			<desc>A map of CSS properties that the animation will move toward.</desc>
		</argument>
		<argument name="options" type="Options">
			<desc>A map of additional options to pass to the method</desc>
		</argument>
	</signature>

	<options>
		<option name="duration" type="Number|String" default="0">
			<desc>A string or number determining how long the animation will run.</desc>
		</option>
		<option name="easing" type="String" default="linear">
			<desc>A string indicating which easing function to use for the transition.</desc>
		</option>
		<option name="complete" type="Function">
			<desc>A function to call once the animation is complete.</desc>
			<!-- no parameters -->
		</option>
		<option name="step" type="Function">
			<desc> A function to be called after each step of the animation.</desc>
			<parameter name="now" type="Number">
				<desc>the numeric value of the property being animated at each step</desc>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="fx" type="Object">
				<desc>the numeric value of the property being animated at each step</desc>
				<property name="elem" type="DOM">
					<desc>the animated element</desc>
				</property>
				<property name="start" type="Number">
					<desc>The first value of the animated property</desc>
				</property>
				<property name="end" type="Number">
					<desc>The last value of the animated property</desc>
				</property>
				<property name="prop" type="String">
					<desc>The property being animated</desc>
				</property>
			</parameter>
		</option>
		<option name="queue" type="Boolean" default="0">
			<desc>A Boolean indicating whether to place the animation in the effects queue. If false, the animation will begin immediately.</desc>
		</option>
		<option name="specialEasing" type="Object" default="0">
			<desc>A map of one or more of the CSS properties defined by the properties argument and their corresponding easing functions (added 1.4).</desc>
		</option>
	</options>

	<!-- no methods -->

	<!-- no events -->

	<desc>Perform a custom animation of a set of CSS properties.</desc>
	<longdesc>The <code>.animate()</code> method allows us to create animation effects on any numeric CSS property. The only required parameter is a map of CSS properties. This map is similar to the one that can be sent to the .css() method, except that the range of properties is more restrictive.

	...

		<section><h3>Per-property Easing</h3><p><![CDATA[
				As of jQuery version 1.4, you can set per-property easing functions within a single .animate() call. In the first version of .animate(), each property can take an array as its value: The first member of the array is the CSS property and the second member is an easing function. If a per-property easing function is not defined for a particular property, it uses the value of the .animate() method's optional easing argument. If the easing argument is not defined, the default swing function is used.

				For example, to simultaneously animate the width and height with the swing easing function and the opacity with the linear easing function:
			]]></p>

			<example src="jquery/animate/examples/per-property.html"/></section>
	</longdesc>
</entry>
